(Sheldon:)No wonder you didn't get
that toothpaste commercial.
- Hey.
(Raj:)I want to apologize for Amy last night.
She was completely out of line.
(Raj:)Are you not speaking to me
or did the screen freeze again?
(Lucy:)Amy wasn't the problem.
(Raj:)Okay, I know, it was me.
(Raj:)I pushed too hard. I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
You know, I've been thinking that maybe
meeting somebody one-on-one...
(Raj:)...is too intense...
(Raj:)...so Friday night,
my friends are having a party.
- A party?
- A little one.
(Raj:)It's a farewell for Leonard,
so all the attention will be on him.
(Raj:)If you wear something brown and sit on the
couch, they won't even know you're there.
- I'm not sure.
- Please.
(Scene:)- Raj.
- Come on, don't make me beg.